# Saebom Pak

### Front-end Developer

- in linkedin.com/in/saebompak
- github.com/saebomp

- (236) 986-5481

## Profile

A self-directed, motivated front-end developer who loves building user-friendly websites and web apps with best practices. Eager to improve development skills with a focus on clean and efficient code. Three years work experience as a UI developer in tech companies, building websites in a collaborative environment

## Skills

JavaScript / HTML5 / CSS / React / React Native / SASS / NPM / GraphQL / Github

## Projects

Kovan / Team project (Front-end developer)

Kovan is an application that manages effectively small groups

#### What I did:

- Built To-do lists and polling pages with React Native
- Implemented interactive graph chart with React Native svg
- Applied consistent styling for expenses page
- Built the promotional website of Kovan with React

#### Result:

- Consistent styling allowed for a seamless user experience
- Interactive graph charts have clean looking visualizations and provide a tool for users to explore data

### o Smart Movie and TV Finder / Personal project

A web app that lets users search for movies and TV shows. Users can browse through their favorite shows

- Utilized RESTful APIs to display movie and tv shows lists upon user's request
- Upon selecting another selection from that dropdown box, the list of results refresh to reflect the updated response from the new query
- Utilized React and Material UI

#### Result:

- Learned how to use React lifecycle methods to create dynamic applications
- Had a good understanding of writing asynchronous requests with Axios

## Saebom Pak / Front-end Developer

### Quick Budget / Personal project

A simple management app that enables users to track their expenses

- It showcases the ability to create expenses and incomes lists and to remove them
- Implemented the calculation functionality the total remaining budget and the total expenses and incomes
- Visualized data with D3.js

#### Result:

- Learned how to bind data to the DOM and its elements

## **Work Experience**

#### Littlefox (Seoul, Korea) / UI Developer

2017 - 2018

- Updated code to improve site performance with HTML 5 and CSS
- Operated across multiple devices and browsers
- Translated designs and wireframes into responsive websites

#### Result:

This work environment allowed the development of communication and interpersonal skills. An enriched understanding of multiple devices was acquired

#### • Whatever Search (Seoul, Korea) / UI Developer

2015 - 2016

- Built responsive websites with HTML, CSS, JQuery and Bootstrap
- Implemented UI for multiple devices according to design
- Transitioned static websites to responsiveness

#### Result:

Able to gain a greater comprehension of responsive web and cross-browsing

#### Gensol Soft (Seoul, Korea) / UI Developer

2014 - 2015

- Built National assembly minutes' website with Web Accessibility guidelines, HTML and CSS
- Built Asiana Airlines' policy manual system front-end with HTML and CSS

#### Result:

Learned how to make a website accessible and became familiar with UX design while transitioning to a user-friendly website. Experienced building a large-scale website

## Education

#### Langara college (Vancouver, B.C.)

Post-Degree Diploma, Web and Mobile App Design and Development / Developer stream